(INDISTINCT MURMURING)
MAN: I'm so sorry for your loss.
WOMAN: Thank you.
(MUFFLED WHISPERING)
And it did make it awkward...
Support us and become VIP member
to remove all ads from www.OpenSubtitles.org
(SCREAMS)
(PHONE CHIMES)
You'll have to be quick.
Yeah. I can be quick.
All good...
Just...
Oh. Lucas. I still have to wear...
I have to wear that.
It's like an oven in here.
OK. Alright.
(PHONE CHIMES)
What?
I forgot. I have a new tenant
arriving at number four. I should go.
I have to give it a spruce.
No. no. no. Let the cleaners do it.
She just seems really fussy.
And I kind of thought about her
for you during the holidays.
Ange...
She asked me if there was a bath
twice.
Ange...
If it's gonna help.
then we need to keep appointments.
you know. make space for us.
Once a week is still good.
I mean. I don't think Fran
and Nigel have had sex in months.
OK.
(GROANS)
I'm good enough.
Open your heart. Drink in the day.
I am good enough.
(DOOR CLOSES)
# I'm just crazy about
the way we move
# Doin' the eagle rock... #
(BEEPING)
WOMAN: Oh. Sorry. mate. that's
declined.
Really?
Um. insufficient funds.
Go to another account?
Just flick it across.
No. That...
I mean. that one should work.
Well. just try it again.
Might be your system. so...
No. It's definitely connected.
Um. sorry. How long is this going
to take? I'm in a bit of a hurry.
Just got some technical issues
with the card. you know?
Sorry.
Mate. You'll have to just come back
with cash. Leave the groceries here.
Well. can't we just try it again?
Because I don't understand
why it's not...
(BEEP)
(BEEPING)
Yeah. let me just...
Maybe I'll use the magnetic strip.
Hey. I can just lend you the cash.
If you just have that phone app
thing. you can transfer me money.
You've got a trustworthy face.
Um. nah. That's insane. No.
Come on. mate. how many times
have I shopped here? You know me.
(SIGHS)
Yes.
Yeah. Are you serious about it?
Thank you.
That's fine.
How much do you need?
Um...
$200?
Yeah. that's...
That should be plenty.
(CLEARS THROAT)
And my number.
Of course.
118.
Thank you.
Oi.
Yeah.
(CAMERA CLICKS)
In case you don't pay.
(CHUCKLES)
Thank you.
10 bucks.
Thanks.
AUTOMATED VOICE:
You have arrived at Pleasant Court.
Isabelle.
Yes.
Hi. Uh... You're Ange?
Present.
Do you need help with your things?
Any problems at all.
I'm just two doors down.
Your bath is down the hall.
Don't take them myself.
Something about
sitting in your own filth.
How many are joining you? I wasn't
sure how much bed linen to leave.
Oh. no-one. It's just me.
Oh. big house for 'just me'.
So. what are you doing in Osprey?
I'm working.
What do you do?
I'm. uh. I'm writing.
I'm a writer.
Oh. cool. What do you write?
I'm working on a travel piece
for the region.
Yeah. they're saying Osprey Point's
the new Byron Bay.
Oh! We're moving you.
I've just had a cancellation
right by the beach.
Oh. no. I'm fine. actually.
This is... This is so beautiful.
No. but if you're writing about
the beaches.
wouldn't you rather be by the beach?
No. I'd rather be here.
Huh.
How long have you lived here?
Most of my adult life.
Ah.
Where are you from?
Sydney.
I've...
I bet you've seen lots of changes.
Not really.
People here don't like change.
Selfish NIMBYs
who don't want progress and growth.
Anyway. here's your credit card form.
Uh. do you actually mind
if I pay in cash?
It's just easier
when it's a work trip.
Sure. Cash works. Love cash.
(PHONE CHIMES)
Three weeks until schools go back
and I am counting the minutes.
Gotta go. I'll be back.
Yes.
Welcome to your new
home away from home.
What do you mean Elvis wouldn't let
you play with your own ball?
She said it was her football.
Well. it's not hers. It's yours.
Somebody needs to talk to her mothers
about this.
So. what do you boys want for lunch?
Cheese and ham toasties. OK.
Hey. Ange. is everything alright?
Essie's asleep in the car
with George.
Remember that tragedy at the casino?
Do you think Essie's been gambling?
It's not funny. Fran.
God. Looks like a murder/suicide.
No. Never wake a sleeping mother.
That's not the expression.
We're in a heatwave.
Yeah. we are too.
Ange...
Hey.
What's going on?
Nothing.
Thank you.
Rent money. Number four.
Oh. cash. How quaint.
Ha! I'm Isabelle.
Oh. I'm Fran.
Cool.
Yeah.
Great.
See you at seven.
Dinner.
Ah. dinner.
Yes. No. I didn't forget. OK.
(CHUCKLES)
Is she another tenant?
Fran? No. she's a neighbour.
She seems. uh...
She's very...practical.
Well. thank you for that.
Good.
Goodbye.
Bye.
Essie. it's time to head inside.
It's too hot out here.
even with aircon on.
Yep.
(BABY CRIES)
Hi. How'd you go?
Yeah. Good.
Who rents a four-bedroom house
when they're on their own?
Hey. I might go for a quick surf
before dinner.
Swell has really picked up.
There's a nice cross offshore.
The tenant at number four.
What does she need
four bedrooms for?
Don't know. babe. Don't know.
Are these eschalots?
Hey. before I forget...
These. I think these are shallots.
No. Aren't shallots
the little brown ones?
No. They're eschalots.
At least where I'm from.
It's fine. I'll go back.
I have to pop into the office.
Hey. before I forget...
Can you keep the boys off screens?
Ange. wait.
(VACUUM CLEANER WHIRRS)
Ange. Ange.
The joint credit card.
It bounced at the store.
That's weird.
Yeah. I've been putting money in.
Yeah. so have I. It mustn't have
cleared. I'll sort it out.
OK. I'll go for a surf
when you get back?
Sure. They're coming at seven.
Can I play online with Jack?
Uh. yeah. mate. go for it.
Actually. uh...
No. Will. no screen time.
What the heck?
Why?
Why don't you practise your layups?
Or you could vacuum.
No.
Who's coming at seven?
Holly and Lulu.
It's been in the calendar for weeks.
And Fran and Nigel.
Eschalots.
Jennifer. did you not see
the protest posters on our window?
No. Where were they?
Literally right in front of you.
Oh...
How'd you go with the renter?
Fine.
She's writing an article on the town.
Thinks it's the new Byron Bay.
Bit of a stretch.
Who's it for?
Good question. Forgot to ask.
What's her name?
Isabelle Ackner.
A-C-K-N-E-R.
There's nothing under that by-line.
Maybe she writes
under a male pseudonym.
A lot of women did that.
In the 19th century.
How are things here?
Any calls? Holiday rentals?
Clive Murphy wants you
to meet him at the cafe in...now.
Oh. Jennifer.
why don't I like the sound of this?
He's probably seen
all the anti-Eureka posters.
Again.
Exactly what I don't want to hear.
Can you clean this window
while I'm gone?
There's eucalyptus oil in the back.
(DOOR SLAMS)
Clive. What can I do for you?
I'm out.
Wow. Can I order a coffee first?
Double espresso. please.
You're out because of a few posters?
It's one person.
There's a whole alliance of them
insisting that the development
of this project
will ruin the environment.
It's a last-ditch nuisance
from a bunch of oldies
who don't want the town to grow.
Well. they have a council hearing.
Well. only because the council is
required to review their objection.
It's a formality. that's all.
I assure you. I have a very strong
relationship with Councillor Foley.
He and I used to...
Doesn't matter.
My daughter. she's into animals.
birds that migrate. emus...
The developers hired
environmental consultants.
The council has approved everything
to date.
Well. she says
the wetlands are going to be...
Eureka will have its own wetlands.
It's all part
of the development plan.
You can be involved with that
as an owner.
Your daughter too. if she wants.
Man-made wetlands aren't the same.
Clive...
..Eureka is a bespoke development.
Just 10 properties.
And yours is the only one I'm
selling. The only one available.
You bought it
because you're a smart businessman.
I'm still within
the cooling-off period.
Don't make a decision you'll regret.
OK. I'll give it
to the council hearing.
But if this mess
is not cleared up by then...
It will be.
..I'm out
and I want my deposit back.
Got it?
Got it.
Good.
(CAMERA CLICKS)
I think your chain's come off.
I can fix it if you want.
I'm the chain expert. Yeah.
What's your name?
Oliver Lucas Romero.
Oh. wow. Oliver Lucas Romero.
I'm Isabelle.
Where do you live?
Over there.
What are you. like. 12? 13?
I'm eight.
You're eight! Get out of here!
How old are you?
Oh...
I'm 38.
Wow. You're old.
Oh. gee. Thanks.
How old's your mum?
32.
Huh? She's young.
I think my dad's 56.
His name is Lucas.
Lucas.
And my brother's name is Will.
And he's 10.
Ah. well.
A family of spring chickens.
Except for your poor old dad.
Alright. All fixed.
Thank you.
Yeah. You're welcome.
(ON RADIO) ..region remains
sweltering...
..temperatures over
40 degrees Celsius.
The Bureau of Meteorology...
Hey. dinner at Ange's tonight.
It's in the calendar.
Is it?
Yeah.
I don't think so.
Yeah. Nothing but Rosie's piano.
Nigel.
It's diplodocus.
Can you call me Daddy. please?
Our calendars mustn't be syncing.
I'll have to fix that.
The brachiosauruses. Right here.
Can you see the difference?
You can say
I've got something else on.
What? No. it's Ange.
She'll want all the details.
And not even I can make up a lie
that far fetched.
Oh. darling. you've got this
the wrong way round.
Mummy. No.
Sorry. I can't help myself.
Come on. Nige.
don't be so anti-social. Please.
I'm not being anti-social. Fran.
I'm being clinically depressed.
But when you're out. you're great.
You're much better than I am.
People have said that.
Who said that?
I don't know. Someone. Once.
Exactly.
Fine. Stay in. I'll make an excuse.
..you are urged to seek
urgent medical.
I'll come.
I'll come. I'll even get changed.
The Bureau is forecasting
above-average temperatures.
I tidied my desk.
Good job. What about your floor?
Get back there. I can't remember
if you have carpet or floorboards.
Mum. it's the holidays.
Yep. Holiday from school.
not from life.
(CHOPS QUICKLY)
Oh. shit.
Uh. would you mind running a rego?
What case is it under?
Actually. it's a welfare check.
Missing persons?
Yeah. something like that.
Do you know the model?
Uh. 77 Triumph.
MAN: Love your car.
Mmm.
Thanks. I'm Isabelle.
I'm here for a few weeks.
I'm Ben.
It's a 2500. right?
Yep.
What's the acceleration like?
Oh. it's slow.
Mmm.
You can take it for a spin
if you want.
Oh. I'd love to.
but I've got to get inside.
You've got the baby. Yeah?
Yeah. And the six year old.
Ah...
Yeah.
Must be something in the water.
This cul-de-sac is literally
crawling with children.
Yeah. (CHUCKLES)
(LULLABY PLAYS)
Open the tunnel. it's Puffing
Billy coming to the tunnel.
She's not a baby. Mum.
Oh. well. I can't stay here
all night. So much to do.
Did he go down alright?
Yeah.
It's midnight when he wants to party.
Evening. my ladies.
Hello.
Hi.
Hello. Hello.
Mwah.
Hi. Barbie.
Hey. hey.
That name.
it's banned in this house.
There you go.
Is he down already?
Yeah. Just now.
How was he today?
The same.
Yeah? How long did he sleep for?
I don't know.
It's a blur. I think I might have
day/night confusion as well.
I'm starving.
Didn't you get any lunch?
Yeah. I did. I went to Holly's and I
got one of those plant-based things.
I mean. it was tasty.
but I could have eaten
about five kebabs straight after it.
Well. the way
we're treating the earth.
we'll all be plant based soon.
Don't scare him. Mum.
Oh. hey. I met the new renter
across the road.
Said I could take her car
for a spin.
She's a beauty.
The renter or the car?
OK. missy-moo. time for a bath.
I think you'll like her.
I mean.
you could do with some friends
who can speak in complete sentences.
What you reading there. Ezz?
The latest Spotlight catalogue.
Mmm.
This one's good.
I'm gonna take this to bed.
(CHILDREN SQUABBLING)
Give me one.
No.
You're gonna have to take it.
I'm juggling.
(INDISTINCT CONVERSATION)
..on my property.
(LAUGHTER)
No. I'm not into developments.
but I'm excited about Eureka.
I think it's good.
Really?
What about the impact it's going
to have on the native wetlands?
You can't tell me
it's not going to have one.
Oh. Nigel. The developers conducted
an environmental assessment
and found no significant issues.
Yeah. I mean. of course they did.
because they're a pack of
See You Next Tuesdays.
(LAUGHTER)
The council was also satisfied.
Everything was fine until Barb
and her friends started agitating.
Well. she doesn't just sell houses.
It looks magnificent.
Mmm.
Oh. don't start yet.
I've got to get the pasta.
Tools down.
Yep.
Can I start on the potatoes?
Is that alright?
Yeah. Get stuck in.
OK. OK.
(LAUGHTER)
There we are.
OK.
Eschalot pasta for the vegans.
We used to be the lesbians.
Now we're the vegans.
That's progress.
Is it?
Darling.
Thank you.
I hope it's not overcooked. It's
intimidating cooking for a chef.
No. Sit down. Shut up. It looks...
Looks really good.
Yeah. it really does. Ange.
So. why are Ben and Essie not here?
Well. how else can we talk
about this properly?
I mean. if we want better schools
and more reliable infrastructure.
this town needs to grow.
I agree. but I also support
an independent impact study.
Oh. shit. I forgot the dill.
You are not allowed to eat
that fish.
No. not until we get the dill. No.
That's mine.
Oh. no.
Yeah.
Hey. how is. um. the new studio.
Lucas?
Um. that's a great question.
It's. uh...
It's going great.
He's going to start doing family
portraits. if anyone's keen.
Yeah.
Yeah. yeah. Sign us up.
Cool.
Elvis broke it.
Oh.
Oh. that took me
a full weekend to build.
It's from the Architecture Series.
Does he do that every night?
He likes washing up.
Says it helps him wind down.
Wind down from fucking what?
Surfing?
Oh. shush.
Sorry?
Speaking of winding down.
how's the thesis going?
That was a terrible segue.
I'm so sorry.
It's OK.
Uh. it's still going.
Oh. mate. you've been writing that
for. um. what?
Four years.
Which isn't uncommon.
You know. um. some PhDs
can take decades to complete.
So...
Yeah.
What's it about again?
Uh. it's about erotic language
in 20th century literature.
Oh. So romantic.
I need to read more.
So. like. academic porn?
Ah... It's funny.
Yeah. yeah. No. it's. um.
it's not as sexy as that.
It's a little bit more nuanced. too.
So...
Bet bedtime is fun at yours.
Can I join?
Mum!
Mum?
Yeah.
There's an old lady here.
Do we know her?
Isabelle.
Hey. Sorry. sorry.
I didn't know you were entertaining.
What?
Hey! My God.
What are you doing here?
Oh. Small world.
Uh. well. I'm renting number four.
Right.
Yeah.
Hi. Hello. Uh. Isabelle.
Holly.
Lulu.
Hi.
Sorry. You two know each other?
Yeah. Well. yeah. we...
Yeah. we met earlier at the store.
and. um. she paid for the groceries
when the credit card bounced.
It didn't bounce.
Oh. and I totally forgot
to transfer you the money.
Oh. no.
I'm sorry.
Do we have any cash?
I'm sorry?
Didn't she give you
a wad of cash earlier?
I reckon at the very least.
we owe you a drink.
I think you should sit down.
Yeah.
Yeah. Oh. no. It's really late.
I'm going to pour her a drink.
Oh. OK.
Thank you.
That's... Yeah.
I didn't come here to get the money.
I actually.
the aircon is not working.
Oh.
Yeah. Kind of melting in there.
so...
Right.
Um. do you have a spare fan
or anything I could borrow?
Yeah. yeah. I'll grab it.
NIGEL: Um. that was. uh.
absolutely delicious. Ange.
Uh. but I think I'm gonna head off.
Oh. What about dessert?
Oh. uh. watching my hips.
Mm. You stay. I'll put Rosie to bed.
It's probably the batteries
in the remote.
I'm sure I checked it. though.
It's fine.
OK. Um. night-night.
And. uh. yeah. Thank you.
Good to see you guys.
Um. thank you again.
It's really delicious.
And. uh. nice to meet you.
See you.
Ah. perfect. Good. Thank you.
Thanks for the wine. Mmm.
Do you need a hand?
Oh. I'm OK.
No. she's strong as an ox.
Oh. look at me go.
Watch the door on your...
(DOOR SLAMS)
Yeah.
Oh. sorry.
Elvis!
OK.
Yeah.
We should go
before she destroys the joint.
Yeah. I'll walk you out and.
uh. check on the boys.
Thank you. See ya.
Thanks.
Night. Night.
(KEYBOARD CLACKS)
(DOOR OPENS)
Morning.
That was weird last night.
What was?
Isabelle turning up.
You two having met.
You never told me.
Honestly. Just slipped my mind.
Boys. brekkie. Come on.
She isn't on social media.
Who's not?
Isabelle.
Oh...
Bit of a red flag.
Sit down. Cereal? Yes?
Yes.
Yes. Great.
Well. I don't know. Maybe
she's not big on photos or videos.
She isn't on any of them.
Well. maybe she's too cool
for social.
Can I Facebook?
Me too.
Uh. no. 'cause it's for
uncool adults like Mummy.
Ah.
Can you drop Will at Sam's
on the way to the beach?
He has a play date.
Yes.
Can I have a play date too?
Yes. You can play on the court.
Yes!
Oh. Oh. yeah.
Playing on the court.
Put your hands in the air.
Oh. yeah. Oh. hey. Will. heads up.
Ollie. Here we go.
Hey. Ollie. did you get some?
OK.
Oh. me...
Watch each other's shots.
I think Mia's winning right now.
How come Mia's winning?
She's got. like. nearly five in.
Whoa.
That was a good shot.
Hey. Ollie. you gonna introduce me
to your friends?
That's Rosie.
Hi. Rosie.
Hi.
Are you in school yet?
No. it's the holidays.
I'm in school.
You are?
What's your name?
Mia.
And my dad says I'm going to prep
with Elvis.
Oh. so cool.
Nigel's depressed.
Oh.
Who's Nigel?
Her daddy.
Rosie. wait for me!
Bye. Mia.
Bye.
Nice to meet you.
And you are?
Elvis.
Elvis. That is a cool name.
Hey. what's your favourite
Elvis song?
Hello. children of the court.
Hello. swish.
Are you too cool for Facebook?
What? What makes you say that?
My dad said it.
What else did your parents
say about me?
That you're a red flag.
What?
You're a red flag.
Hi. I'm Ange from Ange's Agency.
A little about me.
My husband and I decided to... No.
(MUTTERS TO HERSELF)
..about me...husband.
I love it here.
My husband and I decided to raise
our boys in Osprey Point
because we love it here.
We enjoy going to the beach.
going on long bushwalks.
playing tennis.
I'm actually club president.
Oh. fuck. Community.
OK. Get involved.
OK.
Hi. I'm Ange from Ange's Agency.
It's crap. Um...
Sell the dream. Sell the dream.
What separates me
from the competition?
I like to get to know my clients.
Secondly. I'm fun.
Go again. OK.
Reset.
I like to get to know my clients.
Second. I'm fun.
Whether you're buying or selling.
let's have a good time.
Lastly. I'm good at my job.
Ange's Agency. bringing you home.
(CHUCKLES)
You right. buddy?
I was with my friends.
but I have asthma.
Ah. Me too.
Do you have your puffer handy?
Here. I'll help you. Come on.
Ah. It's a big hill. isn't it?
Hold your breath.
And...let go.
(EXHALES)
Yeah. Why don't you just have
a rest now?
On here.
Good. OK.
What the fuck?
Hi.
Um. I'm looking
for Will's skateboard.
What are you doing in my house?
He had an asthma attack.
I brought him home.
Is he alright? Will? Will.
OK. Are you alright?
I'm fine. Yeah.
I'll. uh. leave you guys to it.
then.
She helped me find my puffer.
Why are you being weird?
I'm not being weird.
LUCAS: G'day. How are you going?
Fran's outside.
The girls have called wine o'clock.
What's going on?
Why are you being weird?
I'm not being weird.
She was in my house uninvited.
I thought you said Will let her in.
I feel... I feel violated.
I mean. she helped your son.
Isn't that a good thing?
Will's 10. He doesn't need help
with his puffer.
It all felt very...
Don't you find it strange that
a writer is not on social media?
Yeah. very. Writers are usually
the first to promote themselves.
I dated one once.
Incredibly narcissistic.
Yeah. I don't find it
all that strange.
I mean.
plenty of credible journalists
prefer to fly under the radar.
Oh. Ollie. Oliver. honey. don't.
You'll get bitten.
She's torturing insects again.
Well. she's not a sociopath.
Darling. maybe don't hurt the ants.
Yeah?
I couldn't find any trace of her
online.
And do credible journos
write travel pieces?
Yeah. of course they do.
It's a plum gig.
I mean. who wouldn't want
to fly business class
and stay in all the best hotels?
Exactly.
Well. I think she seems nice enough.
Who seems nice enough?
Isabelle. The tenant at four.
Oh. Ben said she's beautiful.
Oh. she's not that beautiful.
She is.
Poor woman.
if only she knew paying in cash
would cause such mass hysteria.
Who uses cash these days?
Drug dealers.
Sex workers.
Babysitters.
Women on the run.
Yep.
Exactly.
Just saying.
Mmm.
(FAN WHIRRS)
Ollie.
I want to watch something.
Where's your dad?
He's gone for a surf.
Get dressed. We've gotta go.
Where?
To work.
Oh.
Yeah.
Alright. boys. in you get.
Right.
Just a sec.
Stay here. OK.
See how you like it.
What a pig!
(DOOR SLAMS)
What are you doing in here?
I came to return the money we owe you
and to look at the AC.
Why do you have this?
I'm sorry. but surely this is a
breach of our tenancy agreement.
Oh. but it's OK for you
to break into my house.
I was helping your son.
Well. I didn't want to leave cash
in the letterbox.
Why are you writing down my family?
My kids?
I was looking at the local property
market for my story.
I saw that you run
an annual street party.
so I thought. great.
what a good time to come visit.
That's a private event for residents.
Oh. well.
in here you say everyone's welcome.
Others can come.
If they bring a plate.
That doesn't explain
why you're writing down
the ages of everyone in my family.
It's research. Ange.
Your family is just a sample of a
street. which is a sample of a town.
Believe me. if I'd known
I'd get the Spanish Inquisition.
I would have gone to a different
place than the Great Ocean Road
to write about.
Do you really want to write a story
about the local property market?
Alright. boys. Out.
Go kick a ball.
What with?
I don't know. sweetheart. Use
your imagination. A pine cone.
OK. right. We're going this way.
Mmm.
This will all be paved.
Lovely.
Eureka is a small development.
but it still means
10 families will be able to live
in this highly sought after
coastal paradise.
I imagine there's
a fair bit of pushback from locals.
environmentalists.
People get proprietorial
in paradise.
They don't want to share.
but they have no right
to sabotage a development
that's got all the proper approvals
when there's a housing crisis
in this country.
Put that in your article.
(PHONE RINGS)
Sorry.
I'll let you get that.
Chuck it.
Did you see that? One handed?
Did you see that?
Yes.
Go on. chuck it.
Three. Two. One.
Ah! Whoa! Too easy.
This heat's driving me crazy.
Yeah. but this time next year.
we'll be sipping on cocktails.
dipping our toes in the pool.
or we'll just be in it.
You know?
I think we should wait.
Might be over capitalising.
What?
You were close to digging
the hole yourself last week.
Yeah. well. this year's been tough.
Setting up your business.
ironing out the kinks in mine.
Sales market's dead.
Yeah. I mean. it's fine by me.
I've got the beach.
Hey. Ange.
you're amazing with money.
OK. Like all of this?
All of it is because of you.
So whatever you want to do.
I'm fine.
What I want is
to not have to do shitty rentals.
I really need your business
to start pulling in money. Lucas.
Will's got private school next year.
We have two mortgages.
Yeah. OK. OK.
But I didn't want or need
the studio. I'm barely there.
Well. you should be.
Portraits make money.
Why did you turn
your location settings off?
Why are you checking my phone?
Because you don't
communicate with me.
(PHONE CHIMES)
Great. Sex alert. Perfect timing.
It's not a sex alert.
It's an intimacy alert.
Let's do it.
Let's do intimacy?
Yeah.
I don't want to.
Twice a week is one too many.
Well. we didn't do it last time.
remember?
It's too hot.
(PHONE RINGS)
(PHONE CONTINUES RINGING)
I've been trying you for days.
Are you OK?
You'd tell me
if there was anything going on.
Yeah.
That's my baby.
It was an accident. I just forgot.
Nobody needs to know.
They accidentally paid it
into a personal account.
Have you told Lucas
you've done this?
What does he do?
He's a photographer
when he's not surfing.
So not much then.
(LAUGHS)
She hung out with.
That girl next door all day.
What's wrong with that?
Oh. nothing.
Are you writing an article?
Oh. you heard about that too?
Small court. people talk.
Sometimes I wish
I had never let you and Ben
talk me into moving back here.
Honestly.
Captions by Red Bee Media
Copyright
Australian Broadcasting Corporation
Do you want subtitles for any video?
-=[ ai.OpenSubtitles.com ]=-